- 麦瑟尔先生 - 这里 就在夹克这里
- Mr. Maisel... -Right there, right on the jacket.
- 一个手印 不是我的 - 我知道
- A handprint. Not my handprint. - I know.
但我夹克现在成这样了
But it is my jacket, which is now ruined
因为这里 左手边
because right there, left hand,
- 很明显 - 我会查出
- clear as day. - I'll find out...
我要你找出这个该死的手印是谁弄的
I want you to find out whose goddamn handprint that is,
然后带过来见我 明白了吗 好吗 好的
and you bring him to me. Yes? Good? Great.
干的好 女士们
Good work, ladies.
- 保持下去 - 爸
- Keep 'em hum, hum, humming along. - Pop?
我就爱听这机器运转的声音
Love to hear the sound of the machines.
- 你看起来没病啊 - 爸
- You don't look sick. - Pop?
康复了
Miraculous recovery?
现代科学的又一大奇迹吗
Modern science score another knockout?
- 我没病 - 是吗
- I'm not sick. - That's not what I heard.
可我听说你病了 钉住
I heard you were sick. Pin.
安静
Quiet.
亲家母一小时前打电话给我
Mother-in-law called an hour ago,
说家里每个人都病了 每个人
said everyone in the family is sick. Everyone.